var questions = [
  {
    num: 1,
    question: "1: What does CSS stand for?",
    answer: "Cascading Style Sheets",
    Option: [
      "Computer Style Sheets",
      "Creative Style Sheets",
      "Colorful Style Sheets",
      "Cascading Style Sheets",
    ],
  },
  {
    num: 2,
    question: "2: How do you select an element with id 'example' in CSS?",
    answer: "#example",
    Option: [".example", "element.example", "#example", "*example"],
  },
  {
    num: 3,
    question: "3: Which property is used to change the text color in CSS?",
    answer: "color",
    Option: ["text-color", "font-color", "color", "foreground-color"],
  },
  {
    num: 4,
    question: "4: What is the default value of the 'position' property in CSS?",
    answer: "static",
    Option: ["relative", "fixed", "absolute", "static"],
  },
  {
    num: 5,
    question:
      "5: How do you specify a border-radius in CSS to create a rounded element?",
    answer: "border-radius: 10px;",
    Option: [
      "rounded: 10px;",
      "border-round: 10px;",
      "border-curve: 10px;",
      "border-radius: 10px;",
    ],
  },
  {
    num: 6,
    question:
      "6: Which CSS property is used to control the space between letters in a text?",
    answer: "letter-spacing",
    Option: ["word-spacing", "line-spacing", "text-spacing", "letter-spacing"],
  },
  {
    num: 7,
    question: "7: What does the 'float' property in CSS do?",
    answer:
      "Specifies whether an element should float to the left, right, or none",
    Option: [
      "Specifies the opacity of an element",
      "Specifies the z-index of an element",
      "Specifies whether an element should float to the left, right, or none",
      "Specifies the rotation angle of an element",
    ],
  },
  {
    num: 8,
    question: "8: How do you include an external CSS file in an HTML document?",
    answer: "link rel='stylesheet' href='styles.css'",
    Option: [
      " style src='styles.css",
      " css link='styles.css",
      " link rel='stylesheet' href='styles.css",
      " script src='styles.css",
    ],
  },
  {
    num: 9,
    question: "9: What is the purpose of the 'z-index' property in CSS?",
    answer: "Specifies the stacking order of positioned elements",
    Option: [
      "Specifies the transparency of an element",
      "Specifies the font size of an element",
      "Specifies the stacking order of positioned elements",
      "Specifies the margin of an element",
    ],
  },
  {
    num: 10,
    question:
      "10: Which CSS property is used to control the spacing between cells in a table?",
    answer: "border-spacing",
    Option: ["cell-spacing", "table-spacing", "border-spacing", "cell-margin"],
  },
];
